Preliminary Guide to the Washington State University College of Engineering Research Division Correspondence, Minutes, Reports, and Speeches circa 1940s-1970
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Redesign and Rebuild Contour Modeling Machine (Box 35, Folder 1731)
- Police Investigation (Box 35, Folder 1732)
- Arson (Box 35, Folder 1733)
- Chemical and Physical Analysis of Metal Parts (Box 35, Folder 1734)
- Report on the Moisture Conditions of the Diatomic Depostis Near Burke, Washington (Box 35, Folder 1735)
- Diatomaceous Earth Investigation for U.S. Bureau of Reclamation (Box 35, Folder 1736)
- Diatomaceous Earth Investigation for U.S. Bureau of Reclamation (Box 35, Folder 1737)
- Soil Test for U.S. Forest Service (Box 35, Folder 1738)
- Ionosphere Measurements for IGY (Box 35, Folder 1739)
- Universal Automatic Air Pollution Recorder (Box 35, Folder 1740)
- Universal Automatic Air Pollution Recorder (Box 35, Folder 1741)
- Kenite Corp. vs. United States (Box 35, Folder 1742)
- Infrared Analyses (Box 35, Folder 1743)
- Diesel Fuel Analysis (Box 35, Folder 1744)
- ** Investigation of Bloating Properties of Pitchstone (??) (Box 35, Folder 1745)
- Sphaerotilus Control for Irrigation Water (Box 35, Folder 1746)
- Sphaerotilus Control for Irrigation Water (Box 35, Folder 1747)
- Fire Investigation (Box 35, Folder 1748)
- Fluoride Analysis (Box 35, Folder 1749)
- Arsenic Content of Hair, Nails and Beard (Box 35, Folder 1750)
- Arsenic Analysis (Box 35, Folder 1751)
- Arsenic Analysis (Box 35, Folder 1752)
- Acid Throwing Case - Spokane Police Department (Box 35, Folder 1753)
- Acid Throwing Case - Spokane Police Department (Box 35, Folder 1754)
- Arsenic Analysis W.S.C. (Box 35, Folder 1755)
- Arsenic Analysis N.S.C. (Box 35, Folder 1756)
- Comparison of Caifornia Determination Methods (Box 35, Folder 1757)
- Chemical Analysis of Black Sand Fractions (Box 35, Folder 1758)
- Chemical Analysis of Black Sand Fractions (Box 35, Folder 1759)
- Arson (Box 35, Folder 1760)
- Test Unloading Pressure of 2 Safety Valves (Box 35, Folder 1761)
- Test Unloading Pressure of 2 Safety Valves (Box 35, Folder 1762)
- Consolidation Test for Washington Testing Laboratories (Box 35, Folder 1763)
- Tests on Sand Blast Sand (Box 35, Folder 1764)
- X-ray Difraction Studies on Cement (Box 35, Folder 1765)
- X-ray Difraction Studies on Cement (Box 35, Folder 1766)
- Triaxial Shear and Unit Density Tests on Soil Samples (Washington Testing Laboratories) (Box 35, Folder 1767)
- Soil Consolidation (Box 35, Folder 1768)
- Glue-Line Quality Tests of Laminated Cedar Decking (Box 35, Folder 1769)
- Testing and Evaluation of Laminated Cedar Decking (Box 35, Folder 1770)
- Diagnosis of Glue Failure in Laminated Cedar Decking (Box 35, Folder 1771)
- Diagnosis of Glue Failure in Laminated Cedar Decking (Box 35, Folder 1772)
- Geologic Search for a Natural Storage Reservoir for Gas (Box 35, Folder 1773)
- Dam Model Study Laboratory (Box 35, Folder 1774)
- Comparative Efficiency Test "Miracle" Heater and Dry Resistance Heater (Box 35, Folder 1775)
- Water Analysis (Box 35, Folder 1776)
- Test of Grading Ring to BPA Specifications (Box 35, Folder 1777)
- Screen Test on Mercury Ore (Box 35, Folder 1778)
- Analyzer Study of Yakima Water Supply System (Box 35, Folder 1779)
- ** Engineering Foundation Cor. Electric Power Needs of the Future (Box 36, Folder 1780)
- Engineering Research Foundation - Earthquake Conference (Box 36, Folder 1781)
- Evaluation of Representative Inland Empire Wood Spcies (Box 36, Folder 1782)
- Hydraulic Model Studies of Hell's Canyon Left Spillway (Box 36, Folder 1783)
- Correction Factors for Vibrational Parameters (Box 36, Folder 1784)
- Development of Nondestructive Testing Devices (Box 36, Folder 1785)
- ** Design and Fabrication of Stress Wave Lumber Grading Machine (Box 36, Folder 1786)
- ** Design of Stress-Wave Lumber-Grading Machine (Box 36, Folder 1787)
- ** Calibration of Kaier (?) (Box 36, Folder 1788)
- Geophysical Borehole Logging (Box 36, Folder 1789)
- Oxidation Tests on Molibdenum Alloys (Box 37, Folder 1790)
- The Development and Evaluation of High Temperature Dry Film Lubricants (Boeing) (Box 37, Folder 1791)
- The Development and Evaluation of High Temperature Dry Film Lubricants (Boeing) (Box 37, Folder 1792)
- Development and Design Criteria for a Dry-film Lubricated Bearing System (Box 37, Folder 1793)
- Development and Design Criteria for a Dry-film Lubricated Bearing System (Box 37, Folder 1794)
- Development and Design Criteria for a Dry-film Lubricated Bearing System (Box 37, Folder 1795)
- Development and Design Criteria for a Dry-film Lubricated Bearing System (Box 37, Folder 1796)
- Development and Design Criteria for a Dry-film Lubricated Bearing System (Box 37, Folder 1797)
- Development and Design Criteria for a Dry-film Lubricated Bearing System (Box 37, Folder 1798)
- Development and Design Criteria for a Dry-film Lubricated Bearing System for the Boeing Airplane Company (Box 37, Folder 1799)
- Development and Design Criteria for a Dry-film Lubricated Bearing System (Box 37, Folder 1800)
- High Temperature Lubricants for Space Vehicles (Box 37, Folder 1801)
- Development of a Vibrational Non-destructive Test for Construction Lumber (Box 37, Folder 1802)
- Development of a Vibrational Non-destructive Test for Construction Lumber (Box 37, Folder 1803)
- Design and Construction of a Torque Screw Pole Tester (Box 37, Folder 1804)
- Pressing Fiber Mats (Box 37, Folder 1805)
- Arson Investigation (Box 37, Folder 1806)
- Preliminary Evaluation of the Vibrating Principle in the Brown Board-Farming Machine (Box 37, Folder 1807)
- **Flapreg Floor Tile (Box 37, Folder 1808)
- Exploratory Particleboards and Fiberboards of Oak (Box 37, Folder 1809)
- Investigation of Cartridge Primers (Box 37, Folder 1810)
- Grain Size Control for .22 Caliber Cartridge (Cascade Cartridge, Inc.) (Box 37, Folder 1811)
- Century 21 Model Exhibition of Columbia Basin - Preliminary (Box 37, Folder 1812)
- Manometer Board (Box 37, Folder 1813)
- Analysis of Well Waters in Orondo, Pine Creek Areas, Chelan, Washington (Box 37, Folder 1814)
- Corrosion Survey of Buried Steel Pipe (Box 37, Folder 1815)
- Effects of Vortices on Stresses in Spillway Gate Structure Rocky Reach Project (Box 37, Folder 1816)
- Development of Process for Manufacture of Corrective Typewriter Ribbon (Box 37, Folder 1817)
- Study on Venus Type Cigat;ette Holder (Box 37, Folder 1818)
- Pete Clausen (Box 37, Folder 1819)
- Investigate Anesthetic Explosion (Box 37, Folder 1820)
- Police Investigation: Accidental Explosion (Box 37, Folder 1821)
- Anaysis of Grain Samples for Poison (Box 37, Folder 1822)
- Spectral Transmittance of Glass (Box 37, Folder 1823)
- Radio Frequency Attenuation Measurements of Shielded Room (Box 37, Folder 1824)
- Radio Frequency Attenuation Measurements of Shielded Room (Box 37, Folder 1825)
- Sheriff Lloyd Daily Ferry County (Box 37, Folder 1826)
- Analyze Furnace Problem (Box 37, Folder 1827)
- Police Investigation (Box 37, Folder 1828)
- River Model of the Diamond Gardner Mill Site (Box 37, Folder 1829)
- River Model of the Diamond Gardner Mill Site (Box 37, Folder 1830)
- Police Investigation (Box 37, Folder 1831)
- Evaluation of Later Glues for Radio Frequency Applications in Edge and End Gluing (Box 37, Folder 1832)
- Preparation of 41x4' Flakeboards (Box 37, Folder 1833)
- Developments of Surplus Cereal Flour for Use in the Woods Products Industry (Box 37, Folder 1834)
- Investigation of Deposits on Airplanes (Box 37, Folder 1835)
- Noxon Rapids Gate Operation Model (Box 37, Folder 1836)
- Investigate Condensate Problem in Light Fixture (Box 37, Folder 1837)
- Police Investigation (Box 37, Folder 1838)
- Investigate Sample of Yogurt for Poison (Box 37, Folder 1839)
- Oil Analysis (Box 37, Folder 1840)
- Research on Fanner Vibration Damper (Box 37, Folder 1841)
- Police Investigation: Burglary (Box 37, Folder 1842)
- Development of High Temperature Stiffening Agent for Glass Screen (Box 37, Folder 1843)
- Analysis and Identification of Various Mineral Instalations (Box 37, Folder 1844)
- Unifine Flour Mill Sta"tos and Water Jacket (Box 37, Folder 1845)
- Urifine Flour Mill (Leonard Fulton) (Box 37, Folder 1846)
- Design, Development and Research Contract DDR-95 Hydralic Model Studies - 100DR Downcomer (Box 37, Folder 1847)
- Design, Development and Research Contract DDR-95 Hydraulic Model Studies - 100DR Downcomer (Box 37, Folder 1848)
- Hydraulic Testing Studies Downcomer Orifice Plate and Cross-header Expansion Joint (Box 37, Folder 1849)
- Hydraulic Testing Studies - Rear-face Piping Configuration (Box 37, Folder 1850)
- Hydraulic Testing Studies - Inlet to K-Downcomer DDR-135 (Box 37, Folder 1851)
- Analytical Services - Export System Pipelines - 100 and 200 Areas (Special Agreement SA-115) (Box 37, Folder 1852)
- Separation and Identification of Compounds Absorbed from Gasoline and Glu-Klen (Box 37, Folder 1853)
- Separation and Identification of Compounds Absorbed from Gasoline by Glo-Klen (Box 37, Folder 1854)
- Analysis for IPC (Box 37, Folder 1855)
- Investigation of Poisoned Meat (Box 37, Folder 1856)
- Closure Studies - Wanapums Development (Box 37, Folder 1857)
- Wanapum Fish Passage (Box 37, Folder 1858)
- Treatment Tests on Power Line Poles (Box 37, Folder 1859)
- Spectrographic Analysis of Stainless Steel Samples (Box 37, Folder 1860)
- **Comparison Analysis of Monels (Box 37, Folder 1861)
- Liver Analysis (Box 37, Folder 1862)
- Harvey Bone Analysis (Box 37, Folder 1863)
- Harvey Aluminum company (Box 37, Folder 1864)
- Comprehensive Model of Wanapum Dam (Box 37, Folder 1865)
- Comprehensive Model of Wanapum Dam (Box 37, Folder 1866)
- Petrographic Analysis of Rock Core Samples (Box 37, Folder 1867)
- Spectrochemical Analysis of Ore Sample (Box 37, Folder 1868)
- Boiler Corrosion Investigation (Box 37, Folder 1869)
- Boiler Corrosion Investigation (Box 37, Folder 1870)
- Testing Outboard Motor (Box 37, Folder 1871)
- End-Gluing Lumber (Box 37, Folder 1872)
- Investigation of End Gluing Lumber (Box 37, Folder 1873)
- Infrared Analysis (Alan Homay, M.D., Spokane) (Box 37, Folder 1874)
- Report on the 2500 Watt Engine Heater for Kim Hotstart Co. (Box 37, Folder 1875)
- Spectrochemical and Chemical Study of Rock Samples (Box 37, Folder 1876)
- Infrared Analysis of Grease Smears (Inland Analytical Labortory) 11/7/60 (Box 37, Folder 1877)
- Institute of Technology Movie (Box 37, Folder 1878)
- Institute Movie Project (Box 37, Folder 1879)
- **Complete Analysis of Unknown Particle (Intermountain Claim Serv. L.H. Castle) (Box 37, Folder 1880)
- Oxbow Hydralic Model (Box 37, Folder 1881)
- Oxbow Hydralic Model (Box 37, Folder 1882)
- Linear Expansion of Long-Bell Particle Board (Interntional Paper Co.) (Box 37, Folder 1883)
- Linear Expansion of Long-Bell Particle Board (International Paper Co.) (Box 37, Folder 1884)
- The Relationship of Flake Thickness and Resin Content to Board Strength (Box 37, Folder 1885)
- Development of Special Brick Bonding Compound for Chimney Liners (Box 37, Folder 1886)
- Investigation of a Germicide (Box 37, Folder 1887)
- Soil Analysis (Box 37, Folder 1888)
- Vibration Fatigue Studies on Electric Conductors (Box 37, Folder 1889)
- Vibration Fatigue Studies on Elecric Conductors (Box 37, Folder 1890)
- Police Investigation of Paint Samples (Box 37, Folder 1891)
- Evaluation Test of Rocker Arm Design (Box 37, Folder 1892)
- Evaluation Test of Rocker Arm Design (Box 37, Folder 1893)
- Kodiak Water Distribution Analysis (Box 37, Folder 1894)
- Manufacture of Thin Flakeboard (Box 37, Folder 1895)
- Experimental Laminating of Specialty Lumber Products (Box 37, Folder 1896)
- Analysis of Municipal Water Supply (Box 37, Folder 1897)
- Study of Lithographic Developer (Box 37, Folder 1898)
- Adams 3/74-present (Box 38, Folder 1899)
- Adams 2/72 - 12/72 (Box 38, Folder 1900)
- Proposal (Box 38, Folder 1901)
- **Correspondence - ACt)in - Production of Min. Wool from Coal (Box 38, Folder 1902)
- **Reports - Austin - Production of Min. Wool from Coal (Box 38, Folder 1903)
- Hard - Contract (Box 38, Folder 1904)
- Hard - Correspondence (Box 38, Folder 1905)
- Hard 3/69 - 7/72 Research Projects (Box 38, Folder 1906)
- Mark Adams - Reports (Box 38, Folder 1907)
- Nos. 100-149 Research Project Proposals (Box 38, Folder 1908)
- 139-Water Pollution (Box 38, Folder 1909)
- 140-E Neon Lighting (Box 38, Folder 1910)
- 141-154 (Box 38, Folder 1911)
- 101-135 137 (Box 38, Folder 1912)
- Nos. 250-299 Research Project Proposals (Box 38, Folder 1913)
- Nos. 300-349 Research Project Proposals (Box 38, Folder 1914)
- Adams, Dun - Reports (Box 38, Folder 1915)
- Mark Adams - Report (Box 38, Folder 1916)
- Drum Drier (Box 38, Folder 1917)
- Nos. 150-199 Research Project Proposals (Box 38, Folder 1918)
- Nos.'200-249 Research Project Proposals (Box 38, Folder 1919)
- "How It All Came Out" 1969-1971 (Box 39, Folder 1920)
- 1969-1971 (Box 39, Folder 1921)
- 1969/1971 Biennial Budget Exhibits (Box 39, Folder 1922)
- 29th Annual Report - The Ohio State University Research Foundation (Box 39, Folder 1923)
- Biennial Section Forecasts 1967-1969 (Box 39, Folder 1924)
- 1967/1969 Biennial Budget Exhibits (Box 39, Folder 1925)
- 1965/1967 Biennial Budget Exhibits (Box 39, Folder 1926)
- Rocky Reach Dam Model (Box 40, Folder 1927)
- Thermal Conductivity of Refractory Insulating Sheets (Box 40, Folder 1928)
- **!Grease Oxidation Study of MoS2 Greases (LOOK IT UP) (Box 40, Folder 1929)
- Analysis of Gasoline (Box 40, Folder 1930)
- Preparation of Debittered Pea Flour Sample (Box 40, Folder 1931)
- A Reological Study of Dilatency on Boron-Nitride Silicone Lubricating Greases (Box 40, Folder 1932)
- Critical Evaluation of the Endevco Transmission Line Vibration Damper (Box 40, Folder 1933)
- Arson Investigation (Box 40, Folder 1934)
- A Feasibility Study on Bagasse as a Raw Material for Dry Process Particleboard (Box 40, Folder 1935)
- Preliminary Study on Peat gloss (Box 40, Folder 1936)
- Finch Memorial Hospital - Hospital Investigation (Box 40, Folder 1937)
- Thermal conductivity of Refractory Product (Box 40, Folder 1938)
- Consultation on Research Contract (Box 40, Folder 1939)
- Agreement CA244 for McIlroy Analysis (Box 40, Folder 1940)
- Agreement CA244 for McIlroy Analysis (Box 40, Folder 1941)
- Study of Retread Cements (Box 40, Folder 1942)
- Hydraulic Model Studies for the Calibration of the Rock Island Spillway (Box 40, Folder 1943)
- Hydralic Model Studies for the Calibration of Rock Island Spillway (Box 40, Folder 1944)
- Pulverizing Dolomite (Box 40, Folder 1945)
- Design and Manufacture a Mold for Casting (Box 40, Folder 1946)
- Thermal Conductivity of Refractory Products (Box 40, Folder 1947)
- Thermal Conductivity of Insulating Firebrick (Box 40, Folder 1948)
- Green Fire Brick Company (Box 40, Folder 1949)
- **Preliminary IR Study on Monoglyceride Esters (?) (Box 40, Folder 1950)
- H and W Distributors Trace Elements in Coal (Box 40, Folder 1951)
- Hydraulic Model Studies of the Hell's Canyon Hydroelectric Project (Box 40, Folder 1952)
- Analysis of Compressed Air in SCUBA Tank (Box 40, Folder 1953)
- **Analysis of SrO Sample (Box 40, Folder 1954)
- Carbon Dating (Box 40, Folder 1955)
- Trace Element Analysis of Alfalfa (Box 40, Folder 1958)
- A Meteorological Survey for Air Pollution Potential - Proposed Ideal Cement Company Plant Site (Box 40, Folder 1959)
- A Meteorologica Survey of a Proposed Plant Site for Air Pollution Potential (Box 40, Folder 1960)
- Stainless Steel Filter (Box 40, Folder 1961)
- Preliminary Sandstone Beneficiation (Box 40, Folder 1962)
- Preliminary Study of Methods of Pulp Fiber Identification (Box 40, Folder 1963)
- Quatitative Study of the Fiber Losses in the Sewer Effluent (Box 40, Folder 1964)
- Manufacture of Dry-Process Boards from Bagasse Fiber (Box 40, Folder 1965)
- The Manufacture of Pith-Faced and Fiber-Faced Bagasse Boards (Box 40, Folder 1966)
- A Study of Pitch Faced Bagasse Boards (Box 40, Folder 1967)
- Density-Close Time Relationships on 3-layer Bagasse Boards (Box 40, Folder 1968)
- The Effect of Prepressing on the Properties of Boards Made with Bagasses Fiber (Box 40, Folder 1969)
- Further Studies on the Prepressing Characteristics of Bagasse (Box 40, Folder 1970)
- Comparison of Washed and Unwashed Bagasse Fiber (Box 40, Folder 1971)
- Evaluation of Bagasse Fiber Received from Bauer Bros. (Box 40, Folder 1972)
- Investigation of Lithographic Plates (Box 40, Folder 1973)
- Recovery of Gold from Black Sand (Box 40, Folder 1974)
- Police Investigation, Hit-Run, Malden, Washington (Box 40, Folder 1975)
- Investigation of Industrial Use of Bruce's Eddy Limestone (Box 40, Folder 1976)
- Evaluation of Starch Moisture Measurement Apparatus (Box 40, Folder 1977)
- Design of Instrumentation for Control os Starch Moisture Content (Box 40, Folder 1978)
- Control of Starch Moisture Content (Box 40, Folder 1979)
- ** Head Losses in Irrigation Values Miller and Poston Mfg. Co. (?) (Box 40, Folder 1980)
- Literature Survey of Missile Launching Devices (Box 40, Folder 1981)
- Carbon-Dating of Charcoal Sample (Box 40, Folder 1982)
- Carbon-14 Dating of Water (Box 40, Folder 1983)
- ** Carbon-Dating of Ba(Co3)2 from Water (fix the sub numbers) (Box 40, Folder 1984)
- Well Cofferdam Construction Study (Box 40, Folder 1985)
- Arson Investigation - Moses Lake (Box 40, Folder 1986)
- Carbon Dating, Aswan Dam Project (Box 40, Folder 1987)
- Carbon Dating of Archeological Samples (Box 40, Folder 1988)
- Debittering Pea Flour and Grits (Box 40, Folder 1989)
- Effect of Valence-Electron Density on the Martensitic Transformation Temperature in Alloy (Box 40, Folder 1990)
- Research on Fire Spread-Fire Models (NSF G-16275) (Box 40, Folder 1991)
- Metallurgical Engineering - Load Reports (Box 41, Folder 1992)
- Mining Engineering - Load Reports (Box 41, Folder 1993)
- Faculty Load Reports Agricultural Engineering 1967-68, 68-69, 69-70 (Box 41, Folder 1994)
- Faculty Load Reports Arch. 1967-68, 68-69, 69-70 (Box 41, Folder 1995)
- Faculty Load Reports Chemical Engineering 1967-68, 68-69, 69-70 (Box 41, Folder 1996)
- Faculty Load Reports Civil Engineering 1967-68, 68-69, 69-70 (Box 41, Folder 1997)
- Faculty Load Reports Electrical Engineering 1967-68, 68-69, 69-70 (Box 41, Folder 1998)
- Faculty Load Reports Mechanical Engineering 1967-68, 68-69, 69-70 (Box 41, Folder 1999)
- Faculty Load Reports Metallurgy 1967-68, 68-69, 69-70 (Box 41, Folder 2000)
- Civil Engineering - Load Reports (Box 41, Folder 2001)
- Agricultural Engineering - Load Reports (Box 41, Folder 2002)
- Electrical Engineering - Load Reports (Box 41, Folder 2003)
- Chemical Engineering - Load Reports (Box 41, Folder 2004)
- Architecture - Load Reports (Box 41, Folder 2005)
- Mechanical Engineering - Load Reports (Box 41, Folder 2006)
- Metallurgy - Load Reports (Box 41, Folder 2007)
- Mining - Load Reports (Box 41, Folder 2008)
- Nuclear Technology - A.E.C. Fellowships (Box 41, Folder 2009)
- Agricultural Engineering - Load Reports (Box 41, Folder 2010)
- Architectural Engineering - Load Reports (Box 41, Folder 2011)
- Chemical Engineering - Load Reports (Box 41, Folder 2012)
- Civil Engineering - Load Reports (Box 41, Folder 2013)
- Electrical Engineering - Load Reports (Box 41, Folder 2014)
- Mechanical Engineering - Load Reports (Box 41, Folder 2015)
- Metallurgy (Box 42, Folder 2016)
- Wood Technology (Box 42, Folder 2017)
- **Spectroscopy and Infra. (Box 42, Folder 2018)
- **Mining Ex. Stat. (Box 42, Folder 2019)
- Metallurgy (Box 43, Folder 2020)
- Wood Technology (Box 43, Folder 2021)
- ** Spectroscopy and Infra. (Box 43, Folder 2022)
- **Mining Ex. Sta. (Box 43, Folder 2023)
- Air Pollution (Box 43, Folder 2024)
- Agricultural Engineering (Box 43, Folder 2025)
- Chemical Engineering (Box 43, Folder 2026)
- ASEE - Mineral Industries (Box 44, Folder 2027)
- ASEE - National Meeting (Box 44, Folder 2028)
- Land Grant College Association - Engineering Division (Box 44, Folder 2029)
- **AIME - American Inst. Min. and Met. Engr. (Box 44, Folder 2030)
- Northwest Mining Association (Box 44, Folder 2031)
- ASM - Teacher's Award (Box 44, Folder 2032)
- Load Report 1953-1964 (Box 44, Folder 2033)
- Deans - Western Engineering Colleges (Box 44, Folder 2034)
- Public Health Service RC-556 (Box 44, Folder 2035)
- Air Force Technical Institute (Box 44, Folder 2036)
- Graduate School (Box 44, Folder 2037)
- **Fellowships, Scholarships and Assist (Box 44, Folder 2038)
- AIME Scholarships (Box 44, Folder 2039)
- Lincoln Arc Welding Foundation (Box 44, Folder 2040)
- Summer Session (Box 44, Folder 2041)
- Business Office Instructions (Box 44, Folder 2042)
- WSC Educational Policies Committee (Box 44, Folder 2043)
- WSC Space Priorities Committee (Box 44, Folder 2044)
- Budgets - DIR (Box 44, Folder 2045)
- Pakistan Project (Box 44, Folder 2046)
- Committee on Instruction (College of Engineering) (Box 44, Folder 2047)
- **Nuclear Tech. Space (Box 44, Folder 2048)
- AEC Grant No. 5 - General (Box 44, Folder 2049)
- **New for Nuclear Tech. (Box 44, Folder 2050)
- Proposal of November 9, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 2051)
- Instructions (Box 44, Folder 2052)
- General Account (Box 44, Folder 2053)
- Nuclear Engineering Laboratory (Box 44, Folder 2054)
- Introduction to Radiochemistry Laboratory (Box 44, Folder 2055)
- Chemical Engineering Laboratory - Project No. 3 (Box 44, Folder 2056)
- Sanitary Engineering Laboratory (Box 44, Folder 2057)
- 1130 (Box 44, Folder 2058)
- Application of Radioisotope Tracer Techniques of the Study of Pulp and Paper Mill Effluents (Box 45, Folder 2059)
- Outdoor Comparison of Vibration on Compresto and Standard Conductors (Box 45, Folder 2060)
- Vibration Decay Tests on 0 in Compresto Conductors (Box 45, Folder 2061)
- ** Outdoor and Indoor Vibration Measurements (Box 45, Folder 2062)
- Study Relating to Lower Snake River (Box 45, Folder 2063)
- Gas Chromatographic Analysis of the Ambient Air (Box 45, Folder 2064)
- Analysis of IQSY Backscatter Radar Observations of F-Region Field-Aligned Irregularities (Box 45, Folder 2065)
- ** Foreign Scientis Fellowship - Dr. Jun Silar (Box 45, Folder 2066)
- Lower Atmosphere-Ionosphere Coupling (Box 45, Folder 2067)
- Piezoelectric Effect on Wood (Box 45, Folder 2068)
- IQSY Polar Ionospheric Echoes (Box 45, Folder 2069)
- Erosion of Surfaces by Impingement of Solid Particles (Box 45, Folder 2070)
- Lower Atmosphere-Ionosphere Coupling (Box 45, Folder 2071)
- Fermi Surface Overlap and Component Thermodynamic Activity (Box 45, Folder 2072)
- Infra-Sonic Waves in the NSF Atmosphere Pacific Northwest (Box 45, Folder 2073)